Prentiss Taylor
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Subject Files, 1885-1991, undated, Series 10:; (Box 3-21, OV 22; 18.0 linear feet; Reels 5913-5935)
  - John Noble and John A. Noble, 1959-1983 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1280-1296)
  - Becky Noell, 1975-1979 (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1298-1312)
  - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences (and Norfolk Society of Arts), 1944-1974, (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5926, Frame 1314-1383)
  - Norfolk Museum of Arts and Sciences (and Norfolk Society of Arts), 1944-1974 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 13-43)
  - Irene Leache Memorial Art Annual Art Exhibition (Norfolk, Virginia), 1944-1949 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 45-72)
  - Dorothy Norman, 1937 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 74-75)
  - Northern Virginia Chapter Hadassah, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 77-78)
  - Northern Virginia Community College, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 80)
  - Northern Virginia Fine Arts Association, 1964-1984 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 82-112)
  - Kendall Northrop, 1924-1953 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 114-125)
  - Norton Gallery and School of Art, 1948 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 127-128)
  - Wayne Nowock, 1952-1954, (2 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 130-186)
  - Richard Bruce Nugent, 1983 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 188-189)
  - C. Nyquist, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 191)
  - George Oakes, 1965-1966 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 193)
  - George D. O'Connell, 1966, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 195-203)
  - Grace Oehser, 1949-1984 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 205-223)
  - Ed Ogul, 1985 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 225-226)
  - Eliot O'Hara, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 228)
  - Oklahoma Art Center, 1942-1969 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 230-233)
  - Oklahoma Museum of Art, 1976 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 235)
  - William Oldaker, 1967 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 237-239)
  - Old Bergen Art Guild, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 241-272)
  - Old Dominion Printing Company, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 274)
  - Marietta M. Olivares, 1983 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 276-277)
  - Lois Olson, 1961 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 279-280)
  - Opera Society of Washington, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 282)
  - John T. O'Rourke, 1965 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 284)
  - Elodie (Courter) and Robert Osborn, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 286-291)
  - Mrs. P., undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 293-294)
  - Rachel Papkin, 1967 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 296-298)
  - Martha and George Parkhurst, 1957-1979 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 300-330)
  - Don Partridge, 1941-1986 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 332-368)
  - Robert B. Patterson, 1966 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 370)
  - Rembrandt Peale, 1938 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 372-381)
  - Samuel Pearce, 1971 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 383)
  - Luciano Pena y Lillo, 1964 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 385-388)
  - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1962-1967 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 390-397)
  - Pennsylvania State University, 1985 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 399-401)
  - Isham W. Perkins, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 403-414)
  - Jack Perlmutter, 1961-1972 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 416-438)
  - William K. Perrin, 1960-1986 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 440-494)
  - Alice Peters, 1960 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 496)
  - Rollo Peters, 1967 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 498)
  - Mabel Peterson, 1980-1983 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 500-507)
  - Egon Petri, 1962 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 509)
  - Edith and Charles Petty, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 511-512)
  - Emelyn Phaup, 1979 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 514)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art, 1953-1976 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 516-537)
  - Philadelphia Water Color Club, 1969-1978 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 539-565)
  - Phillips Collection, 1974-1981 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 567-579)
  - Duncan Phillips, 1966 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 581-587)
  - Betty and Jozef Pielage, 1963-1964 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 589-593)
  - John Michael Pierce, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 595-607)
  - Louis Vergniaud Pierre-Noel, 1973-1982 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 609-611)
  - Josephine Pinckney, 1933-1957, (3 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 613-717)
  - Pitkin County Bank, 1960 (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 719-720)
  - Pittsburgh Art, undated (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 722)
  - Playhouse Gallery, 1948-1959, (8 folders) (Box 13, Reel 5927, Frame 724-997)
  - Playhouse Gallery, 1948-1959, (2 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 999-1087)
  - May Pohl, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1089-1092)
  - Michael Ponce De Leon, 1962-1966 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1094-1110)
  - John A. Pope, 1982 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1112-1113)
  - Mrs. James Porter, undated (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1115)
  - Katherine Anne Porter, 1980 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1117-1118)
  - Leslie Portner, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1120-1122)
  - Ezra Pound, 1954-1962 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1124-1164)
  - Ginevra and Phil Portlock, 1981 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1166-1168)
  - Potomac Art Therapy Association, 1978 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1170-1173)
  - Richard Powell, 1986 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1175-1182)
  - Rudy Pozzatti, 1958-1959 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1184-1187)
  - Pratt Graphic Art Center (Pratt Center for Contemporary Printmaking), 1959-1977 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1189-1206)
  - Dody Prentice, 1980 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1208-1211)
  - Karl Prieve, 1976 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1213)
  - Hartwell Priest, 1971-1975 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1215-1219)
  - Print Club of Albany, 1958-1984, (4 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1221-1357)
  - The Print Club (Philadelphia), 1979 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1359-1361)
  - Print Council of America, 1958-1961 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1363-1384)
  - E. R. Purves, 1964 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1386)
  - Pynson Printers, 1933 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1388-1389)
  - Roderick Quiroz, 1960-1979 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1391-1434)
  - Rosa Sotelo Quiroz, 1963-1965 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1436-1437)
  - Mary de Rachewiltz, undated (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1439)
  - Railway Express Agency, 1960 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1441)
  - Francisco Ramirez, 1961 (Box 14, Reel 5927, Frame 1443-1446)
  - Arnold Rampersad, 1980-1985 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 13-34)
  - Mary Reardon, 1977 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 36-40)
  - Olivia Redfield, 1966 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 42-43)
  - Edward Reed, 1911-1975, (5 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 45-310)
  - Jesse F. Reed, 1971-1974 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 312-318)
  - Albert Reese (see also Kennedy Galleries), 1975-1982 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 320-363)
  - Frank K. M. Rehn, Inc., 1937-1938 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 365-369)
  - William P. Reimann, 1975 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 371-376)
  - Fritz Reiner, 1963 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 378)
  - Helen and Leonard Rennie, 1961-1981 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 380-389)
  - Armando Reveron, 1956 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 391-404)
  - Ruth Rhetts, 1976 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 406-407)
  - Anthony Rice, 1982 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 409-410)
  - Jeanne Herron Richards, 1964-1977 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 412-439)
  - Helen Riegle, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 441-444)
  - Fred Ritter, 1933 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 446)
  - Edward G. Robinson, 1953 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 448-453)
  - Mary Turlay Robinson, 1972 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 455-458)
  - Rockville Art Gallery, 1961 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 460)
  - Roger Rogan, 1973 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 462)
  - John C. "Jack" Rogers, 1965-1979 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 464-474)
  - Joan Root and William Raiford, 1972-1983, (3 folders) (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 476-568)
  - Albert Roothbert, 1965 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 570)
  - James Rorimer, 1966 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 572-575)
  - Milton and Ingrid Rose, 1977-1986 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 577-590)
  - Ruth Starr Rose, 1960-1966 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 592-646)
  - Lillian Rosenthal, 1974 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 648-649)
  - Lessing J. Rosenwald, 1964-1979 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 651-663)
  - Malcolm Ross, 1965 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 665)
  - Mrs. Marvin Ross (Lotus Robb), undated (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 667)
  - Elizabeth E. Roth, 1981-1982 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 669-681)
  - Theodore Roth, 1976 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 683)
  - Delight Rothe, 1964 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 685)
  - Edward William Rothe, 1960-1964 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 687-693)
  - Howard Rothschild, 1975 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 695-696)
  - Randolph S. Rothschild, 1976 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 698-699)
  - Eric Rudd, 1973 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 701-702)
  - Beatrice A. Rudes, 1966 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 704-707)
  - Alexander Russo, 1962-1981 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 709-716)
  - Vincenz Ruzicka, 1960 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 718)
  - Bob and Polly S., 1963-1965 (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 720-722)
  - Martha S., undated (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 724-725)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1945-1991, (18 folders; includes oversized materials from Box 21 and OV 22) (Box 14, Reel 5928, Frame 728-1370)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1945-1991, (5 folders; includes oversized materials from Box 21 and OV 22) (Box 14, Reel 5929, Frame 13-275)
  - St. Elizabeth's Hospital, 1945-1991, (15 folders; includes oversized material from Box 21 and OV 22) (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 277-634)
  - Harry Salpeter, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 636)
  - Ethel and Antrim Samford, 1962 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 638-639)
  - Herbert J. Sanborn, 1966-1975 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 641-646)
  - Lucile H. Sanders, 1968-1979 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 648-673)
  - Isaac J. Sanger, 1953-1975 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 675-684)
  - Frances Herriott Sargent, 1966-1972 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 686-691)
  - Robert Sargent, 1977 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 693)
  - Martha and Bob Sauer, 1964-1978 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 695-711)
  - Daniel C. Sayre, 1956 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 713)
  - Concetta Scaravaglione, 1975 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 715)
  - Alice Pauline Schafer, 1960-1980 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 717-735)
  - Bertram Schaffner, 1956-1960 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 737-739)
  - Louis Schanker, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 741-742)
  - Constance Scharff, 1971-1977 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 744-756)
  - Ernest Schein, 1963 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 758)
  - Paula Schoenhof, 1969 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 760-765)
  - Grace M. Schumaker, 1965-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 767-774)
  - Ambassador Schurmann, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 776)
  - Bella Schwartz, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 778-779)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Scott-Hall, 1964 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 781)
  - Louise Seabury, 1972-1976 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 783-785)
  - Mary Secombe, 1933 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 787)
  - Security Storage Company, 1978 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 788-805)
  - Daniel Serra-Badu, 1963-1976 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 807-824)
  - Martha Severens, 1985 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 826)
  - Seton Guild, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 828-829)
  - Marion Severn, 1932 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 831-832)
  - Polly Shackleton, 1979 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 834)
  - Helen Shaffer, 1978 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 836)
  - Hilda Shapiro, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 838-839)
  - J. B. Sharpton, 1946 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 841)
  - Murray Sheehan, 1963 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 843)
  - Charles Sheeler, 1983 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 845-846)
  - Roslyn Shelesnyak, 1962 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 848-849)
  - Ernest Shepard, 1977 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 851)
  - Sheppard and Enoch Pratt Hospital, 1973 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 853-854)
  - Roberta Shoemaker, 1976 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 856-857)
  - William H. Shoemaker, 1976 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 859)
  - Lily Shuff, 1966-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 861-863)
  - Forrest Shuster, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 865-866)
  - Sidwell Friends School, 1958-1986 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 868-875)
  - Sidwell Friends School, 1958-1986 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 877-878)
  - Norman Singer, 1960-1973 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 881-887)
  - John C. Sirica, 1972-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 889-915)
  - Ruth and Bob Sivard, 1972-1984 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 917-932)
  - Ross W. Sloniker, 1960 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 934-935)
  - Chard Powers Smith and Eunice Clark Smith, 1961-1983 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 937-972)
  - Charles Smith, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 974)
  - David Smith, undated (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 976)
  - David Smith (sculptor), 1965 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 978)
  - Gordon and Sue Smith, 1964 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 980-981)
  - Helen B. Smith, 1963 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 983)
  - Joe Smith, 1960-1961 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 985-986)
  - Katherine Smith, 1969-1974 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 988-992)
  - Nannette Smith, 1960-1980 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 994-1055)
  - Smithsonian Institution (U.S. National Museum), 1948-1966 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1057-1068)
  - Smithsonian Institution Traveling Exhibition Service, 1972 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1070)
  - Society of American Graphic Artists, 1960-1984 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1072-1142)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers) Minutes of Meetings, 1934-1960 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1145-1192)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers) Accounts Ledger, 1939-1961 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1194-1229)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers) Miscellaneous Business Records, 1934-1979 (Box 15, Reel 5929, Frame 1233-1353)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers), 1934-1979, (12 folders) (Box 15, Reel 5930, Frame 13-512)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers), 1934-1979, (30 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5930, Frame 514-1434)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers), 1934-1979, (21 folders) (Box 16, Reel 5931, Frame 13-525)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers), 1934-1979, (13 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 527-903)
  - Society of Washington Printmakers (Society of Washington Etchers) Photograph Album, 1960-1978, (13 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 905-917)
  - Southern Graphics Council, 1983 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 919-920)
  - Raymond Sovey, 1966 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 921)
  - Raphael Soyer, 1980-1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 923-928)
  - Dominic Spadaro, 1966 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 930-933)
  - Kathleen Spagnolo and Frank Spagnolo, 1969-1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 935-964)
  - Spink and Gaborc, Inc., 1978 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 966-969)
  - Mary Smith Sprowls, 1957 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 971)
  - Benton Spruance, 1963 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 973-975)
  - James R. Stabenau, 1963 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 977-981)
  - Shelby and Peter Stancioff, 1972 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 983-984)
  - Aubrey Huntington Starke, 1960-1970 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 986-1012)
  - Dorothy Starr, 1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1013)
  - Ruth Stauffer, 1965 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1014)
  - William and Leslie Stearns, 1933-1937 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1016-1026)
  - Gertrude Stein, 1934-1935 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1028-1049)
  - Steinlen, undated (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1051-1054)
  - Bertrice Stern, 1969 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1056-1057)
  - Edith Stern, 1975 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1059)
  - Harold Stern, 1977 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1061)
  - Herbert M. Stern, 1977 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1063-1064)
  - Frances Sternhagen, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1066-1067)
  - Ami C. Stewart, 1978 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1069)
  - Leverett and Virginia Stone, 1980 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1071-1075)
  - Paul Strand, 1976 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1077-1079)
  - Marjory Strauss, 1977 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1081)
  - Victoria Price Street, 1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1083)
  - Strike 400, Inc., undated (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1085-1087)
  - William Strickland, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1089-1111)
  - L. Corrin Strong and Alice Trowbridge Strong, 1956-1964 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1113-1170)
  - Henry Strong, 1978 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1172-1173)
  - Robert Stubbs, 1964 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1175)
  - Ronald and Joan Stuckey, 1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1177-1181)
  - Studio Gallery, 1957-1980 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1183-1194)
  - Studio House, 1934 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1196-1197)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1979 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1199-1200)
  - Henry Sugimoto, 1966-1974 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1202-1220)
  - Philip B. Sullivan, 1957 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1222-1231)
  - T. A. Sullivan and Sons, 1973 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1233)
  - Ben Long Summerford, 1975 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1235-1236)
  - Katherine Summy, 1961 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1238-1244)
  - Estelle Sumner, 1936-1948 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1246-1249)
  - Beth Sundquist, 1982 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1251)
  - Ruth H. Sutton, 1956 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1253-1256)
  - Bill Suworoff, 1976 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1258)
  - Genevieve Sykes, 1958 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1260)
  - Tamarind Lithography Workshop, 1963-1978 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1262-1275)
  - Helen N. Tate, 1955-1977 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1277-1341)
  - Liz Tate, undated (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1343-1344)
  - Ann R. Taylor, 1965-1980 (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1346-1355)
  - Beatrice H. Taylor (mother of Prentiss Taylor), 1926-1954, (2 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5931, Frame 1357-1395)
  - Beatrice H. Taylor (mother of Prentiss Taylor), 1926-1954, (21 folders) (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 13-559)
  - Bessie Taylor, 1932-1962 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 561-563)
  - John Eastlack Taylor, Jr., 1944-1978 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 565-577)
  - Joshua Taylor, 1981 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 579-586)
  - Mary Taylor, undated (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 588-589)
  - Sarah Alberta Taylor, 1914-1966 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 591-605)
  - Douglas H. Teller, 1970 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 607)
  - Theater Chamber Players, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 609-613)
  - Edmund Thompson, 1958 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 615-616)
  - Myrtle Fish Thompson, 1958 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 618)
  - Hilda Thorpe, 1975-1979 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 620-625)
  - Arthur Thrall, 1960-1963 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 627-646)
  - "Three Recent Lithographs" Brochure, 1968 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 648-672)
  - Frederic Thursz, 1959 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 674-678)
  - Tidewater Artists, 1955 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 680)
  - T. Tilney, 1954 (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 682-683)
  - Tirca Karlis Galleries, undated (Box 17, Reel 5932, Frame 685-686)
  - Josiah and Anne Parrish Titzell, 1927-1957, (5 folders) (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 689-882)
  - Walter N. Tobriner, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 884-886)
  - Alice B. Toklas, 1947-1980 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 888-910)
  - Anthony Toney, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 912-913)
  - Dottie Berger Tormey, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 915-918)
  - Jennie Tourel, 1959-1973 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 920-928)
  - Yvonne Townsend, undated (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 930-935)
  - Place Trams, 1979 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 937-938)
  - Norman Treigle, 1975 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 940)
  - Mrs. Lanta Trent, 1957 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 942)
  - Pauline Trimpi, 1966 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 944-945)
  - Juan Trippe, 1981 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 947)
  - A. Buel Trowbridge, 1959-1981 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 949-951)
  - C. K. Trueblood, 1974 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 952)
  - Don Turano, undated (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 954-955)
  - Twentieth Century Club of Washington, D.C., 1962 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 957-959)
  - George T. Tyler, 1960-1973 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 961-966)
  - Raymond E. Tyner, 1950-1968 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 968-1017)
  - Helen D. Tyrrell, 1971 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1019-1023)
  - Ansei Uchima, 1962 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1025-1026)
  - Elinor Ulman, 1963 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1028-1029)
  - Ivan Valtchev, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1031-1037)
  - Dorothy H. Van Venschoten, 1982 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1039)
  - Mark and Dorothy Van Doren, 1944-1973 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1041-1050)
  - John Van Druten, 1957 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1051)
  - David Van Fossen, 1955-1963 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1053-1065)
  - Willem Van Loon, undated (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1067-1068)
  - Hildegarde G. Van Roijen, 1973-1981 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1072-1084)
  - Eleanore Van Swearingen, 1957-1966 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1086-1088)
  - Carl Van Vechten Correspondence, 1931-1965 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1091-1130)
  - Carl Van Vechten scrapbook of letters, 1931-1932 (Box 18, Reel 5932, Frame 1132-1405)
  - Carl Van Vechten Correspondence, 1920-1965 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 14-29)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Van Vechten, 1932, (Includes oversized materials from Box 21) (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 31-41)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Unidentified Individuals, 1920-1965 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 43-48)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Max Ewing, 1932-1934 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 50-53)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of W.C. Handy, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 55-56)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Langston Hughes, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 58-63)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of James Weldon Johnson and Grace Nail Johnson, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 65-68)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Rockwell Kent, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 70-71)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Claire Luce (Actress), 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 73-74)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Francis Lederer (Actor), 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 76-79)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Rose McClendon (Actress) (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 81-82)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Colin McPhee, 1933 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 84-85)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Paul Meeves, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 87-88)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Edna St. Vincent Millay, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 90-93)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Eugene O'Neill and Carlotta Montereg, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 95-96)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Frida Kahlo and Diego Rivera, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 98-99)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Bill "Bojangles" Robinson, 1932-1933 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 101-112)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of G.B. Stern, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 114-115)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Sander Szabo (Hungarian strongman), 1933 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 117-122)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of John Van Druten, 1936 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 124-125)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Prentiss Taylor, undated and 1932-1948 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 127-245)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Prentiss Taylor with Jimmie Daniels, Donald Angus and Tonis Selmart, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 247)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Prentiss Taylor with Gladys Bentley and Nora Holt, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 252-255)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Prentiss Taylor with an unidentified man, 1932 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 257-268)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Ethel Waters, 1933 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 270-273)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Boston, n.d. (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 275-297)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Provincetown and Cape Cod, n.d. (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 299-314)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Massachusetts and New Hampshire, n.d. (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 316-331)
  - Carl Van Vechten Photographs of Yale University, n.d. (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 333-350)
  - Carl Van Vechten Miscellaneous Photos, n.d. (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 352-363)
  - Carl Van Vechten Clippings, 1942-1961 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 365-403)
  - Carl Van Vechten Exhibition Catalogs, undated and 1933-1965 (Box 18, Reel 5933, Frame 405-460)